Guide to the Dept. of Government honors theses, 1991-2016
Dept. of Government honors theses, 1991-2016
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Dept. of Government honors theses, 1991-2016
14-16-3477
Cornell University.Dept. of Government.
6.3 cubic ft.
Honors Theses
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Honors theses arranged by year.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Honors theses arranged by year.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Cornell University--Students.; Cornell University.Dept. of Government.; Cornell University.Class of 1991.; Cornell University.Class of 1992.; Cornell University.Class of 1993.; Cornell University.Class of 1994.; Cornell University.Class of 1995.; Cornell University.Class of 1996.; Cornell University.Class of 1997.; Cornell University.Class of 1998.; Cornell University.Class of 1999.; Cornell University.Class of 2000.; Cornell University.Class of 2001.; Cornell University.Class of 2002.; Cornell University.Class of 2003.; Cornell University.Class of 2004.; Cornell University.Class of 2005.; Cornell University.Class of 2006.; Cornell University.Class of 2007.; Cornell University.Class of 2008.; Cornell University.Class of 2009.; Cornell University.Class of 2010.; Cornell University.Class of 2011.; Cornell University.Class of 2012.; Cornell University.Class of 2013.; Cornell University.Class of 2014.; Cornell University.Class of 2015.; Cornell University.Class of 2016.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- The Cyclical Nature of Airline Antitrust Policy by David Einhorn, May 22, 1991 (Box 1)
- From the Bottom Up: Business/Government Relations in the U.S. and Japan by Aaron Pempel, May 1991 (Box 1)
- Towards an Expanding Europe: EFTA's Rush and Resistance by Bronwyn N.P. Dylla, 1992 (Box 1)
- Utopia Unbound: The Social and Political Theory of Herbert Marcuse by Martin Z. Braun, April 13, 1992 (Box 1)
- Representation for the Black Electorate: The Search for Political Equality Reaches a Fork in the Road by Noah Baylin, April 12, 1993 (Box 1)
- The European Convention on Human Rights: A Study of Normative Enforcement by Elaine Tseng, Spring 1993 (Box 1)
- Public Policies, Private Remedies: Product Liability, the Consumer Product Safety Commission, and the Politics of Injury by Sanford C. Gordon, April 11, 1994 (Box 1)
- The Perpetuation of an Inefficient System: The Relationship Between School Finance Inequities and the Political Process in Lake County, Illinois by Michael J. Wiggins, April 10, 1994 (Box 1)
- Lenin and the Ethics of Terror by Steven J. Wulf, April 11, 1994 (Box 1)
- The "Success" of West German Denazification: A Comparative Analysis of West Germany, East Germany and Austria's Value Change in the Post-War Era by Erica Ruth Gould, April 10, 1995 (Box 1)
- Martial Species: Understanding Sikh Ethno-Nationalism by Nirej S. Sekhon, 1995 (Box 1)
- The Domestic Implications of Exchange Decontrol: A Case Study by David L. Bernstein, April 1996 (Box 1)
- Misdeal: How the Federal Government Unintentionally Catalyzed the Greatest Proliferation of Legal Casino Gambling in United States History by Nicholas Goldin, April 15, 1996 (Box 1)
- Russia's Foreign Policy Paradox: Democracy as Anti-Western by Alec Moseley, April 15, 1996 (Box 1)
- Machine Politics: Partisan Uses of Databases and the Internet by Noah J. Goodhart, April 18, 1997 (Box 1)
- The Commodity of Life: Politics, Packaging, and Patenting of Genetic Science by Eric Little, April 1997 (Box 1)
- The Death of the Subject and Its Political Consequences by Richard James, November 23, 1998 (Box 1)
- Prospects for Peace: The Political Context of Northern Ireland's Good Friday Agreement: An Analysis by Emily T. Cope, April 1999 (Box 1)
- Stemming Nuclear Proliferation: The Role of Expectations in a State's Decision Calculus by Sonali Singh, April 17, 2000 (Box 1)
- Conflict Resolution in Enduring Rivalries: The Importance of Political Shocks by Jamie Aycock, April 16, 2001 (Box 4)
- Institutional Bias: A Case Study of Plea Bargaining in Orleans Parish, Louisiana by Olufunke Grace Bankole, April 16, 2001 (Box 1)
- The Art of Rhetorical Manipulation: Legitimating China's Economic Reforms in Official Discourse by Reyko Huang, April 16, 2001 (Box 1)
- The Political Role of Religion in America: a Tocquevillian Perspective by Grace Kim, April 18, 2001 (Box 1)
- Native Hawaiian Sovereignty: The Tragedy of Displacement by David A. Minami, April 2001 (Box 1)
- An Institutional Theory of Third Party Politics by Amy Rachel Gershkoff, April 2002 (Box 1)
- Refinements to the Opportunistic Political Business Cycle Theory by Byron Hing, April 18, 2002 (Box 1)
- Sexuality, Family, and Citizenship: An Intervention in Queer and Feminist Theory by Adam Phillip Romero, April 18, 2002 (Box 1)
- No Buses in Bugtussle: Regionalism and the Failure of Fuel Taxation Policy in America by Christopher Angevine, April 17, 2003 (Box 1)
- The Partisan Politics of Ex-Felon Disenfranchisement Laws by Jason Belmont Conn, April 2003 (Box 1)
- Economic Shift and Political Fallout: The Impact of Liberalization on Indian Politics by Ganesh Karunakaran, April 17, 2003 (Box 1)
- Israeli Military Actions and Diversionary Behavior by Hania Kronfol, Fall 2003 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Gulag: A Trauma Archipelago by Livia Kusa, April 2003 (Box 2)
- The Two Faces of International Assistance: NATO and EU Involvement in Central and Eastern Europe by Tsveta Petrova, April 2003 (Box 2)
- Institutionalization in a Period of Prisoners' Rights Retrenchment: States' Responses to Lewis v. Casey by Jo Anne Galardy, April 2004 (Box 2)
- Animal Rights and Human Morality: Achieving Normative Consensus through a Contractualist Deliberative Framework by Bradley Dax Grossman, April 2004 (Box 2)
- The Solicitor General's Political Role as Amicus Curiae in the United States Supreme Court by Brian Schartz, April 22, 2004 (Box 2)
- Deprived of Rights, Detained, and Deported: Unaccompanied Alien Children in the United States 1984-2004 by Alison Rose Levine, April 26, 2004 (Box 2)
- Settlement & Paralysis: The Split Personality of Ethnic Conflict in the Post-Soviet States by Ilya Shulman, April 19, 2004 (Box 2)
- The Effects of Employment and Unemployment on Voting Preferences in the 2004 Presidential Election by William Hausberg, April 18, 2005 (Box 2)
- Strategies of Democracy Promotion: Are Non-Governmental Organizations Effective? by Julia Levy, April 18, 2005 (Box 2)
- The Christian Right, The Christian Left, and United States Foreign Policy by Daniel Parker, April 2005 (Box 2)
- From Strauss to Lacan, From Intention to Desire: Two Methods of Reading Through Machiavelli's "The Prince" by Michael Stanish, Spring 2005 (Box 2)
- Fighting Justices: Personal Animosity and Decision-Making on the United States Supreme Court by Catherine Suh, Spring 2005 (Box 2)
- Nathan Nagy, "Radical Reform: Institutional Resistance to the Prison Litigation Reform Act", 2006 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Michelle Cassorla, "What's on TV Tonight? An Analysis of the Television Campaign of Advertisements of Male or Female Political Candidates", 2007 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Andrew Ng, "Accompanying the King: Building a Democratic Governance State in Morocco", 2007 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Amy Saltzman, "Contested Fields: Agrarian Discourse in Contemporary Farm Debates", 2007 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Paul Testa, "Iran's Quest for Nuclear Power and Status: Prestige Motives in Nuclear Proliferation", 2007 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Jason Beekman, "The Price Tag for Civil Rights: 'Pay as You Go' Prisoner Access to the Courts", 2008 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Junchen Hong, "Squaring the Circle: State Capitalism and Singapore's Government-Linked Companies" (2 copies), 2008 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Jason Stern, "The Online Israeli-Palestinian Conflict: How Authority Shapes Public Spheres on the Internet", 2008 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Ariel White, "Performing Gender at the Podium: 'Women's Language' in Gubernatorial Debates", 2009 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Jaime Winkelman, "The American Response to the International Criminal Court: The Application of International Relations Theory and Subsequent Implications", 2003 (Box 2)
- Ch-Yuan Kaiy Quek, "Face Value and Foreign Policy: China and the Taiwan Strait Crises, 1995-1999", 2005 (Box 2)
- David Kiferbaum, "From Provision to Power: Challenges to the State from Religious Non-Governmental Organizations in the Middle East", 2008 (Box 2)
- Julia Lippman, "What Rocks The Vote: Explaining State Variation of Young Voter Turnout Rates", 2008 (Box 2)
- Sung Wook Kim, "The Vicissitudes of United States Policy toward North Korea Policy and the Sources of United States Foreign Policy", 2008 (Box 2)
- Leonard Rubin, "Compromise and Controversy: The Perplexing Origins of No Child Left Behind", 2008 (Box 2)
- Josh Goldstein, "Cross-Party Presidential Tickets: Frequently Considered, Never Realized, But Formidable Nonetheless", 2009 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Ari Freilich, "Mr. Smith Hates Washington: Cultural Intimacy, Savior Citizens, and the Politics of Naivety in Modern America", 2009 (Box 3)
- Jeremy D. Campbell, "Pragmatic Policy Adjustment in Congress Following Landslide Presidential Defeats: The Republicans 1964-1966 and the Democrats 1972-1974", 2009 (Box 3)
- Luis-Francois de Lencquesaing, "A World of Financial Models", 2009 (Box 3)
- Alexandra Pavel, "Unexpected Presidents and Their Legacies in the Twentieth Century: Patterns in 'Accidental' Succession", 2009 (Box 3)
- Roxana Larin, "Assessing the Breakdown of FTAA Negotiations as a Result of Ideational Incompatibility: A Statistical Analysis", 2009 (Box 3)
- Larissa Eltsefon, "Russia and the European Union: Identity and Policy in the Post-Soviet Space", 2009 (Box 3)
- Aaron Q. Weinstein, "The Religionsmiths: An Examination of Neoconservatism's Engagement with the Tree Monotheistic Faiths", 2009 (Box 3)
- Madeline Rose Snider, "Rethinking Migration and Security: The Indispensability of Legalization in the Quest to Make America Safer", 2009 (Box 3)
- Cassandra Robertson, "Free to Submit: A Foucauldian Analysis of Women's Rights and the New Modern in Morocco", 2009 (Box 3)
- Robert Bertorelli, "Enemies in All Those Whom You have Injured" Economic Ties, Transformation, and Political Protest, 2009 (Box 3)
- Maury Slevin, "A Nuclear Iran: Who Fears It? Who Welcomes It? An Analysis of the Security Council's Response to Iran's Nuclear Program", 2009 (Box 3)
- Noah Grynberg, "From Subject to Participant? The Development of German Political Culture in the Postwar Era", 2009 (Box 3)
- Virginia McGowan, "The 'Faithful Voter': Catholics, the Democratic Party, and United States Presidential Elections Since 1952", 2009 (Box 3)
- Alma Isavel Arnedo Aldric, "Women, Health, and Power: Examining the Relationship Between Women's Healthcare and Women's Representation in Sub-Saharan Africa", 2010 (Box 3)
- Neha Aviral, "The United States of America and the Islamic Republic of Iran", 2010 (Box 3)
- Elie Bilmes, "The Politics of Corrections: Partisanship and Incarceration at the State Level, 1980-2002", 2010 (Box 3)
- Kimberly Brody, "Path Dependency and Suthoritarian Legacies: Institutions, Human Rights, and Chile's Transition to Democracy", 2010 (Box 3)
- Carrie Bronsther, "Systematic Sexual Violence during War: An Analysis of Violence against Women in Israel/Palestine, Sri Lanka, and Sudan", 2010 (Box 3)
- Elizabeth Curran, "Fleeing Persecution? The Politics of Immigration and Asylum Policymaking in the United States and Canada", 2010 (Box 3)
- Isabel Cutting, "Foreign Aid in the National Interest: A Model of Bilateral Development Assistance in Sub-Saharan Africa", 2010 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Donial Dastgir, "Clever Humility: An Analysis of the Importance of Cultural Artifice in Iranian Society and Politics", 2010 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Rahul Desai, "Midterm Loss: Examining the Relationship between Presidential Agendas and Midterm Election Outcomes", 2010 (Box 3)
- Felipe Gomez-Herrera, "Not Just About Drugs: The United States War on Drugs, Plan Colombia, and the Merida Initiative", 2010 (Box 3)
- William Hart, "The Psychological Construction of the SOviet Threat: A Study in the Making of United States Soviet Policy from 1945 to 1947", 2010 (Box 3)
- Junrong Keith Koh, "Unity in Autonomy", 2010 (Box 3)
- Rian Masanoff, "Paradox Confirmed: A Test of Daniel Drezner's Theory on the Efficacy of Economic Statecraft in International Relations with New Data from 1998-2008", 2010 (Box 3)
- Kate Meyer, "Systematic Violence and Regional Human Rights Systems", 2010 (Box 3)
- Reid Pauly, "Containing the Atom: Paul Nitze and the Tradition of Non-Use of Nuclear Weapons", 2010 (Box 3)
- Ethan Pollack, "United States Foreign Policy Toward the Cold War Middle East: An Analytic Narrative (1948-1973)", 2010 (Box 3)
- Matthew V. Rotbart, "All Politics is Local -- Even the Politics of War", 2010 (Box 3)
- Michael J. Schillawski, "The Financial Geography of the Presidency: 1992-2008", 2010 (Box 3)
- Daniel J. Smith, "Financial Crises and the Expansion of Executive Power in the United States", 2010 (Box 3)
- Harin C. Song, "Transitional Justice: A Comparative and Theoretical Analysis", 2010 (Box 4)
- Brett Michael Waldron, "Rethinking Constitutional Precommitment: Imagining An American Nation in the Name of the People", 2010 (Box 4)
- Gillian Bader, "Income Inequality, Firearm Availablility and Homicide Rates: A New Conception of the 'More Guns, More Murder' Argument", 2011 (Box 4)
- Bradley Bartlett, "How 'Originalist' Were the Original Supreme Court Justices?", 2011 (Box 4)
- Theresa Cederoth, "The Emergence of Maverick Supreme Court Justices", 2011 (Box 4)
- Matthew Clemente, "Same-Sex Marriage and the Limits of Liberalism", 2011 (Box 4)
- James Crowell, "Transitioning Autocrats: Why do Democratic Institutions Fail to Prevent Personal Integrity Violations in Anocracies?", 2011 (Box 4)
- Mitchell Drucker, "A Defense of United States Sanctions on Burma", 2011 (Box 4)
- Ross Eisenberg, "Chinese Oil and American Militarization in Africa", 2011 (Box 4)
- Andrea Faldermeyer, "Obscenity 2.0? Internet Pornography and the Development of Contemporary Community Standards", 2011 (Box 4)
- Ali Hussain, "Pakistan: The Islamic Republic for Some", 2011 (Box 4)
- Christine Kim, "Race to the Top: Allocating Federal Education Funding Under the Obama Administration", 2011 (Box 4)
- Esther Kwan, "Strangers in Eretz Yisrael: The Ordeal of Migrant Workers in Israel" (never received), 2011 (Box 4)
- Minkyung Lee, "Judicial Review in Political Context: Korea and Japan", 2011 (Box 4)
- Allen Miller, "American Higher Education in Qatar: Causes and Consequences of the Rise of Satellite Campuses", 2011 (Box 4)
- Elena Moreno, "End of Informal Empire: The Decline of United States Hegemony in Latin America Under the Bush Administration", 2011 (Box 4)
- Kathryn Morisy, "From Soup Kitchens to Soap Boxes: The Relationship Between Islamic Charities and Civic Involvement in Jordan", 2011 (Box 4)
- Bora Park, "What Can You Do For Me? Economic Asymmetry and Bargaining in Economic Transition of Reunified States: Comparing Germany and Vietnam", 2011 (Box 4)
- Zain Pasha, "Atoms for More Atoms: The Proliferation Inducing Potential of Peaceful Nuclear Assistance", 2011 (Box 4)
- Rebecca Richards, "Not Quite What They Were Hoping For: How Western Democracies Condition the Emergence and Persistance of Electoral Authoritarian Regimes", 2011 (Box 4)
- Kyle Rifkind, "Corruption by Design in International Organizations", 2011 (Box 4)
- Matthew Sellars, "A Case Study Analysis Regarding Variables that Lead to Suicide Terrorism in Asymmetric Warfare Involving a Terroist Organization", 2011 (Box 4)
- Holden Steinhauer, "Structural Intelligence Reform in America: The Success of Goldwater-Nichols, the Failure of IRTPA, and a Proposal for Reform", 2011 (Box 4)
- Kayla Strong, "Forcing Silence" How Militarized Drug Policy Compromises Freedom of the Press in Latin America", 2011 (Box 4)
- Daniel Szirmak, "Assessing the Interpretive Effects of the Canadian Federal and Provinicial Governments' Official Multiculturalism Policy on New Immigrants' Political Incorportaion Levels", 2011 (Box 4)
- Jaon Wasser, "Divisive Primaries and the Independent Vote in United States Senate Elections: Moving the Debate Forward", 2011 (Box 4)
- Ryan Woo, "From Chemical Warfare to Cybersecurity: A Comparative Study of United States Interest in 'Use-based' Arms Control", 2011 (Box 4)
- Emily Zhang, "Laid-Off State Workers and the Chinese State: Institutionalization of State- Society Relations through Social Security", 2011 (Box 4)
- Michael Zhang, "Strategic Politics within Federalism's Frameworks: What Post-Enron Delaware Corporate Law Reveals about 21st Century Federalism", 2011 (Box 4)
- Judah Bellin, "Realism Without Cynicism: Considering Reinhold Niebuhr Today", 2012 (Box 4)
- James Bor, "American Dream Foreclosure: Evolution of U.S. Housing Policy from Dwelling Place to Welfare State", 2012 (Box 4)
- Emma Clarke, "Europe's New Scapegoats: the Politics of Anti-Muslim Discourse in the Era of Integration", 2012 (Box 4)
- Anna Collins, "Rethinking Explanations of Secessionist Attempts: A Multi-Method Approach", 2012 (Box 4)
- Charlotte Deng, "Singapore-Malaysia Relations and International Relations Theory", 2012 (Box 5)
- Iris Malone, "Play Nice with the New Kids: A Reassessment of Democratization's Impact on Interstate Conflict", 2012 (Box 5)
- David McCarey, "The Link Between the New York Governorship and the United States Presidency", 2012 (Box 5)
- David Murdter, "Broadcast Deregulation and the Growth of Political Talk Radio", 2012 (Box 5)
- Jonathan Panter, "The Dictator's Playbook: A path-dependent approach to authoritarian protest control policies in the Middle East", 2012 (Box 5)
- Kathleen E. Perkins, "Engendering Justice? Male and Female Judges and Partisan Dynamics on the Federal Appellate Courts", 2012 (Box 5)
- Taskin Rahman, "The Business of War: How U.S. Business Reacts to War Since the 20th Century", 2012 (Box 5)
- Erica Rhodin, "The Consequences of Incorporation: Reform and Heightened Coup Risk in Bolivia", 2012 (Box 5)
- Laura Anne Schwartz, "Censorship and Self-Censorship: China's Influence on Academic Publishing in Hong Kong and Singapore", 2012 (Box 5)
- Katherine Anne Zimmerman, "Electoral Competition, Inequality, and Corruption in the Russian Federation: A Cross-Regional Analysis", 2012 (Box 5)
- Emily Boudreau, “The Veterans Health Administration: Analyzing the Infrastructure Behind Success”, 2013 (Box 5)
- Colin Chan, “Essentialism and Right-wing Populism in the Tea Party: An Analysis of the Tea Party in the Context of the American Right”, 2013 (Box 5)
- Nicole Collins, “The Rise and Fall of Latin American Liberation Theology: The Catholic Church and Progressive Organizing under Authoritarianism”, 2013 (Box 5)
- Bruno de Larragoiti Lucas, “Ain’t too proud to beg: IMF stabilization programs and incumbent reelection prospects”, 2013 (Box 5)
- Samir Doshi, “Are You a Supreme Court Justice: An Analysis of the Ideological Interdependence between the Supreme Court and the Public”, 2013 (Box 5)
- Aaron Glickman, “Privatized Peace? How Private Military and Security Companies May Shape the Future of UN Peacekeeping”, 2013 (Box 5)
- Sarah Greenberg, The French Presidential Elections of 2012: Memory, Communication, and National Identity”, 2013 (Box 5)
- Cindy Huynh, “Asian American Electoral Strategy: Racialized and Deracialized Methods in California State Assembly Campaigns”, 2013 (Box 5)
- Lucia Rafanelli, “National Identity and Normativity in Egyptian and American Constitutionalism”, 2013 (Box 5)
- Andrew D. Santana, “Economic Thought and American Political Development: From Franklin Roosevelt to Barack Obama”, 2013 (Box 5)
- Lauren Davis Schorr, “Resistance ǀ Identity ǀ Liberation: The East Timor and Aceh Conflicts in a Postcolonial Frame”, 2013 (Box 5)
- Joyce Wu, “How Micro-Targeting Shapes Political Knowledge”, 2013 (Box 5)
- Tucker Doherty, “Authoritarian Cyberspaces: Regional Politics and the Internet in Russia and China”, 2014 (Box 5)
- Erin Ellis, “A Vote of Confidence: Retrospective Voting in Africa”, 2014 (Box 5)
- Caroline Emberton, “Let the Punishment Fit the Crime: A Study of Current Practices and Legal Strategies for Enforcing Human Trafficking Laws in Advanced Democracies”, 2014 (Box 5)
- Margaret Henry, “Voting Under Siege: How Liberalism Frames the Franchise”, 2014 (Box 5)
- Laura Jakli, “What's the Matter with Hungary: Post-Accession Hungary and the Breakdown of Democracy”, 2014 (Box 5)
- Srinath Kethireddy Reddy, “The Makings of Monetary Orthodoxy: The Political Economy of Central Bank Independence”, 2014 (Box 5)
- Samuel Kuhn, “Flexibility in Orthodoxy: The Misunderstood Role of Wahhabi Ideology in Preserving the Saudi State”, 2014 (Box 5)
- Sohee Rho, “Confronting the Alien: Immigration Policy and Racial Formation in the United States in 1882, 1924, and 1965”, 2014 (Box 5)
- William Ryan, “Political Sacrilege: The American Catholic Bishops, Catholic Politicians in the Democratic Party and the Politics of Abortion”, 2014 (Box 5)
- Aaron Schifrin, “Constructing Justice: Constitutional Court Architecture in Nascent Democracies”, 2014 (Box 5)
- Russell Silver-Fagan, “The Journey or the Destination: Relative Impacts of Income Change and Current Income on Policy Preferences”, 2014 (Box 5)
- Kirat Singh, “Microfinance Amidst Meltdown: An Inquiry into the role of International Capital Markets in Determining Outcomes for National Microfinance Sectors during the Global Financial Crisis 2008”, 2014 (Box 5)
- Christopher Spencer, “Building a Nation Under Siege: How the Second Chechen War Enabled Centralization and Authoritarianism in Putin's Russia”, 2014 (Box 5)
- Merritt Steele, “Filling a Vacancy: Chicago Communities in Foreclosure”, 2014 (Box 5)
- Zoe Valette, “Panda or Tiger? A New Perspective on Recent Chinese Assertiveness”, 2014 (Box 5)
- Erica Augenstein, "From the Ground Up: Building the GCC Labor Force”, 2015 (Box 6)
- Daniel Byers, "Leading the Blind: How Peer Influence Keeps Voters Loyal and Allows Polarization to Grow”, 2015 (Box 6)
- Bianca Herlitz-Ferguson, "Assessing the Nature of Change: The Supreme Court and Juvenile Sentencing”, 2015 (Box 6)
- Haejin Hwang, "Reshaping the Perspective: A Comparative Study of Long-term Peace in Croatia and East Timor”, 2015 (Box 6)
- Christina Kim, "Policy and Posterity: The Intersection of Intergenerational Justice and Public Policy in the United States”, 2015 (Box 6)
- Justin Lee, "The Theater of War: Presidential Initiative and Congressional Authorizations for Use of Military Force”, 2015 (Box 6)
- Jiali Li, "Between Political Institutionalization and Informality-Anti-corruption Enforcement in China since the 1990s”, 2015 (Box 6)
- Shourou Li, "A Thorough Examination of the Chinese Welfare System followed by Proposals for Changes based on European Experiences”, 2015 (Box 6)
- Terence Looi, "Change Preempted: Barack Obama's Untimely Liberal Rendezvous with a Conservative Political Time, 2015 (Box 6)
- Roberto Matos, "Protective Propensities: Partisan and Ideological Polarization in the Regulatory Implementation of Trade Protection”, 2015 (Box 6)
- David Melly, "Riding Which Wave? Responsiveness and Political Messaging in 2010 Gubernatorial Campaigns”, 2015 (Box 6)
- Michael Alter, "This is Ireland, And So Is That - A Study of the Relationship between State Structure and Violence in 20th Century Ireland", 2016 (Box 6)
- Jinney Chung, "The Race of Life - Race and Citizenship in American Political Thought", 2016 (Box 6)
- Chad Crowley, "Addressing Climate Change: When Do Public-Private Partnerships Succeed?", 2016 (Box 6)
- Yiran Du, "Defining the Boundary - Immigration, Peoplehood, and the Chinese Exclusion Act of 1882", 2016 (Box 6)
- Michelle Fraling, "Help a Sister Out - How Women in Congress are Supporting Female Candidates Through Leadership PACs and Member Donations", 2016 (Box 6)